Guide to the Travel brochure and map collection, [19--].
Travel brochure and map collection, [19--]
- Description: City/ Region, State
  - Greater Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Street Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - IRC Bus Guide: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gulf Niagara Falls Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Niagara Falls Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gulf Niagara Falls Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Standard Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mobil Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Wagner Map: Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Booklet: Turkish and Russian Baths of the Invalids' & Tourists Hotel, Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Book: Standard Road Book/Buffalo section/Good Roads, Buffalo, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Subway Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - World's Fair, 1964-1965: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Esso World Fair Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Esso Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Texaco Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cruises: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hagstrom's Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - AAA Map: NYC, New York (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - St. John's Cathedral: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Museum guide: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Shell Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Principle auto routes: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mobil Travel Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ESSO Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Borough Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mobil Westchester and Putnam map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Socony Westchester and Putnam map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Texaco Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Subway Guide: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Gulf Tourguide map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Subway map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - World Fair subway map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Texaco borough map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Exxon Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Leaflet: Empire State Observatories, NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Guide: Illustrated Guide to the Hudson River and Catskill Mountains (including New York City), NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Book: The Transportation Club, NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Exxon Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Manhattan Bus Guide: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Esso Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Texaco Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - AAA map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - AAA map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Exxon Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mobil Travel Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Triborough bridge and tunnel map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell Inn: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hudson River Day Line: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Delaware, Lackawanna, Western rail guide: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NY Photo collection: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Old NY photo collection: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chelsea Lodging: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn Bridge: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Red Book Information and Guide: Manhattan and Bronx New Sectional Map: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hispanic society collection: NYC, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Yonkers Map: New York State, New York (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - prca (Parks, Recreation & Cultural Affairs Administration) where book: What to do in New York City & how to get there 1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - time table: Delaware Lsackawanna and Western Rail Road, NYC to New York State (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - time table: New York Midland Railroad, NYC - New York State (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - sailing schedule: United American Lines/Hamburg-American Line, NYC - Hamburg (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Socony Map: Finger Lakes, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - United States Survey Company Guide and Map: The Finger Lakes of Central New York, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca Map: Finger Lakes, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca automobile guide: Finger Lakes, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fingerlakes guide: Finger Lakes, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Beautiful Finger Lakes Call You, Central New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Souvenir of the Finger Lakes Region, Central New York, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Finger Lakes Region, Central New York State (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Beautiful Finger Lakes Trails, Central New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Views of Auburn, Central New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Auburn Bus lines schedules, Central New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Canandaigua Steamboat Company, Central New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Tioga Railroad Company, Central New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Glen View Cottage, Watkins, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Old Courthouse brochure: Finger Lakes, Ithaca, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Finger Lakes: Watkins Glen, New York (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Golf Guide: Finger Lakes, New York, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mobil Map: Long Island, New York (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Socony Map: Long Island, New York (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Booklet: Jones Beach State Park, Rockville Centre, New York (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Niagara, summer & winter: Upstate, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Niagara George Belt Line: Upstate, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Niagara rainbow trail: Upstate, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Niagara Falls Tours: New York State, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Niagara, summer & winter: Upstate, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Niagara George Belt Line: Upstate, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Niagara rainbow trail: Upstate, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Turtle: Native American Center for the Living Arts: Niagara Falls, New York (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 21 photographs: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 16 individual postcards: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 16 individual postcards: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 15 individual postcards: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 11 mounted postcards: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 4 mounted photographs: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Niagara in summer and winter (booklet): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Read as You Ride, Niagara Gorge Belt Line (5 leaflets, 2 editions [train]): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Niagara's Great Gorge Trip (2 leaflets [train]): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Niagara Gorge Railroad (leaflet [train]): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Niagara Falls/16 day excursions (leaflet [train]): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Niagara Falls Line, (2 leaflets, 1 card [bus]): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Honeymoon line time table/Buffalo to Niagara Falls: Niagara Falls, New York (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Maid of the Mist (2 editions leaflet [boat]): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Rainbow Trail (highway strip map): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Turtle, Native American Center for the Living Arts (leaflet): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Migration of Niagara Falls (article): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Souvenir of Niagara Falls (pamphlet): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Souvenir of Niagara Falls (fold-out postcards): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sheldon & Hawley's Illustrated Guide to Niagara Falls and Points of Interest: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sheldon & Hawley's Illustrated Guide to Niagara Falls (fold-out postcards): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Souvenir of the International Hotel (pamphlet): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Souvenir Folder of Niagara Falls (2): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Where to go in Niagara Falls This Week, July 7-23, 1927 (pamphlet): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Niagara Falls Tour Map: Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Niagara Falls (panoramic view): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - At the next stop/Niagara Falls power plant (leaflet): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Niagara Falls Power (pamphlet): Niagara Falls (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Geological survey: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Iroquois wildlife preserve (2 leaflets): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Edward's Bus schedule (2): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Central Greyhound schedule/time tables (3 editions): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Greyhound time tables (leaflet): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Blue Bus Lines Time Table (leaflet): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Gould Bus Line: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - State Park Guide: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Trolley Exploring: New York, New Jersey, Upstate New England (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Indian Springs Farms: Baldwinsville, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Historic Houses: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - New York State Vacationlands (2 editions): Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Exploring NY Past: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Canal System map: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Waterford Canal map: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Catskills Map: Upstate New York State (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Route 17 map and guide (leaflet): Upstate New York State (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bennington Battlefield (leaflet): Upstate New York State (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Routes from Kingston and Ashokan Reservoir (map): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - leaflet: Exploring New York's Past, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Empire Tours of New York (map): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - New York and New Jersey tourguide (map): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Popular Priced Resorts Ass'n (leaflet): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - George Eastman Birthplace: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - A Guide to Letchworth Park: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lackawanna Timeteables: Upstate New York State (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Railroad Timetables: Upstate New York State (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - New York Central Railroad ticket book: Upstate New York State (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - This is New York State (guide book): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Historic Landmark Journeys in New York State (pamphlet), Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Historic Sites of New York State(pamphlet), Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Summer in New York (pamphlet), Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Allegany Region: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Allegany State Park: Upstate, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad: New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mothers of the Revolution memorial (pamphlet): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway Power Project (pamphlet): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Onondaga Centennial Souvenir (pamphlet): Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Early History of the Town of Van Buren, Onondaga County: Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Oswego Convict Ship (clipping, pamphlet, photocopy): Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer County Sesqui-Centennial: Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The State Reservation, Saratoga Springs: Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - United States Hotel, Saratoga Springs: Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Catalogue of The Pompeia:a reproduction of the house of Pansa at Pompeii, Saratoga Springs: Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Skyway to U.S.A./The 1000 Islands Bridge/Joining Canada and U.S. (map): Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Troy Your City (pamphlet): Troy, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Minnewaska Mountain Houses (pamphlet): Minnewaska, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Old Fort Niagara: Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - French Castle at Old Fort Niagara: Upstate, New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 3 AGCC Christmas carols: New York State (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Schohanna Trail (Binghamton-Albany and Schenectady): New York State, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pocket Guide Book of Watertown and Northern New York: Upstate, Upstate New York (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Esso map: "Upside-down" map, New York to Florida (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cabin Trails ... (map): New York; Pennsylvania; Province of Ontario, Canada (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cabin Guide (map): New England, New York, Quebec (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo Evening News map: World maps, News Map of the Changing World (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Park Guide: Great Smoky Mountains, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Transportation Map: Entire, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - AAA map: Entire, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - National sea shore guide: Cape Hatteras, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Park Guide: Chimney Rock, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Street Guide: Georgetown, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mountain Guide: Hendersonville + Flatrock, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Grandfather Mountain: Linville, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Grandfather Mountain Highland Games: Linville, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Moravians during the Revolution: Wachovia, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Park guide: Great Smoky Mountains, North Carolina (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Brochure: Theodore Roosevelt Museum, North Dakota (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - AAA guide: Southeastern Canada to St. Louis to Maine, Northeastern Tour Book (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - AAA map: Southwestern Canada and northwestern U.S., Northwestern States and Provinces (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - AAA map: Cleveland, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - AAA map: Cleveland, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Post card: Marblehead, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sohio Map: Entire, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Amish Country: Central, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sohio Map: Entire, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Transportation Map: Entire, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Map: Turnpike, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Humble Map: Entire, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Official Transportation Map: Entire, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mobil Map: Entire, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Railroad Map: Entire, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Indian Museum: Anadarko, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Western map: Oklahoma City, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - National Cowboy Hall of Fame: Oklahoma City, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Wildlife refuge: Wichita Mountain, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Facts: entire state Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lock and Dam: Bonneville, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - National Park Guide: Crater Lake, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - U. S. Dept. of Interior: Crater Lake, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lock and Dam: Dalles, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - National Memorial: Fort Clatson, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Powerplant: FDR Lake, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lock and Dam: John Day, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lock and Dam: McNary, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Museum: Coos-Curry, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Powerplant: Trojan, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Travel Guide: Oregon Coast, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Recreational areas: Entire, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mobil Map: Portland, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lodging: Ashland, Oregon (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Among the Amish: Entire, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Amish Dutch: Entire, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Guide Map: Bethlehem, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brices crossroads/Tupelo, Mississippi (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - (Bus)Blue Ridge Lines Timetable (2 editions): New York State, New York (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - (Bus) Harmony Lines schedule: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania-Cleveland, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cliveden: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Karamac (5 booklets/leaflets): Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Vacation Valley (2): Echo Lake, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Island View Inn (leaflet): Greentown, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hospitality Association: Hershey, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sagamore (booklet): Milford, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Montgomery County (booklet), Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Philadelphia (leaflet), Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Old Bookbinder's Restaurant (booklet), Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia in Fall (leaflet): Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia - old and new (booklet): Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - PRT (Philadelphia Rapid Transit System) route Map: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia's Fairmount Park (leaflet): Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Historic Society Hill (leaflet): Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Wagner's Map: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Esso Map: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - AAA Map: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Exxon Map: Entire, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pictorial Guide + map (Esso): Entire, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Standard Map: Entire, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mobil Map: Pennsylvania, Maryland, Virginia and West Virginia (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Traveler's guide: Los Angeles to Chicago, Route 66 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Travel Adventure: Entire, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Garden and Home Guide: Entire, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Revolution Sites: Entire, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Railroad post Card: Charleston, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Travel Brochure: Charleston, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Walking tour: Charleston, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Camping resort: Lakewood, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Historic East Coast: East, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Historic Inns: Entire, South Carolina (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Drug Stores: Badlands, South Dakota (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - National Park Guide: Wind Cave, South Dakota (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - National Memorial: Mount Rushmore, South Dakota (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - AAA map: Southwestern U. S., Southwestern States (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The De Luxe Golden State Limited,Rock Island Lines/Southern Pacific Lines (railroad), Southwestern U. S., Southwestern States (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - AAA guide: Florida to Canada, Susquehanna Trail (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Choo-Choo Express: Chattanooga, Tennessee (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Indian Trails: Natchez Trace, Tennessee (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Chucaclissa: Memphis, Tennessee (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - National Military Park: Point Park, Tennessee (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Exxon: Entire, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Enco Sightseeing Guide: Entire, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Highway Map: Entire, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - AAA Map: Houston, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - AAA Map: Houston, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - AAA Map: Entire, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Railroad Map: Entire, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Map: Clinton Drive, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - National Park: Guadalupe Mts., Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Natonal sea shore: Padre Islands, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Humble Map: Dallas-Ft. Worth, Texas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fort Martin Scott: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Corpus Christi Bay: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - BB35 Battleship: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Moody Gardens: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Galveston Car Museum: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Galveston Railroad Museum: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Galveston Island history: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Historic Galveston: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Alamo: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Anahuac: National + Historical Parks, Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Standard Oil map: Toll Roads: Illinois, Indiana, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Maryland, Delaware, New Jersey, New York, New England (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - AAA map series: Triptik: Georgia, Florida, Alabama, Louisiana, Texas (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Historic Edition: Arches, Utah (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Esso map: Pocket Atlas, United States (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Conoco: Transcontinental, United States (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - National Geographic Society map: Vacationlands, United States and Southern Canada (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Esso map: Interstate highways, United States (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Eco-friendly note: red roof inns, United States (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Map: Entire, United States (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Map: Entire, United States (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Map: Entire, United States (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Map: Entire, United States (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Map: Entire, United States (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Map: Entire, United States (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Indian Map: Entire, United States (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Map of the United States, Union Pacific System, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cheap railway transportation (booklet): (any state), United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - NY/PE/NJ: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - ILL/IND/OH/KY: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - AZ/NM/UT/CO: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - George Washington rt.: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - WI/MI: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - ND/SD/NEB/KAN/MINN/IO/MISSO: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - CA/NE: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - ARK/OK/LO/TX: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - NH/VER/MASS/RI/CONN: Regional, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Wayside Notes Along the Sunset Route, Southern Pacific System, United States (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Highway Map: Entire, Utah (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Vermont Transit Lines (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Caverns: Luray, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Caverns: Luray, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tourist guides (2): Natural Bridge, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Endless Caverns: Shenandoah Valley, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Living Museum: Newport News, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mariner's Museum: Newport News, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ferries: Norfolk area, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AAA Map: Norfolk, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tunnels: Norfolk- Portsmouth, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk and Western Ry.: Come to Virginia, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk and Western Ry.: Land of Romance, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State History: Entire, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Conservation Commission: The Beckoning Land, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Carry Me Back To Old Virginia (2 editions) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Lodging: Old Point Comfort, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ferries: Jamestown, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sky-Line Drive postcards: Shenandoah National Park, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sky-Line Drive postcards: Shenandoah National Park, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of the Interior guide: Shenandoah National Park, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of the Interior map: Shenandoah National Park, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Guide: Massanutten Caverns, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Nasa: Wallops Island, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)